http://www.woodworkweb.com/privacy-statement.html

Privacy
Details
Hits: 36333
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used at Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans. We take extraordinary steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. Information Collection Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans is the sole owner of the information collected from our website. We do not, or will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in our privacy statement below.
Cookies A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. Advertisers connected to Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans at times require cookies to tract statistics about products and locations, but at no time are these linked to any personal identification. At this time, Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans uses cookies.
Log Files Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans keeps log files on broad fields to analyze trends, track user movements, and gather data for demographic locations. This is not attached in anyway to visitor's personal identification.
Sharing At this time, Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans does not share any information with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party.
Links Links to other sites outside of Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans do not apply to this privacy statement. We are not responsible for privacy policies of other websites linked to Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans. Please read the privacy statement of each website linked to Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans for information and data use for visitor's personal identification. Our privacy statement applies solely to Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans.
Contests At any particular time, Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans will conduct contests for our visitor's. Visitor participation for these contests is voluntary, and in no way requires the visitor to give out personal information when choosing not to enter in the contest. Collected information may include contact information and demographic information, such as name, e-mail, address, state, ect. This information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.  Sending to a Friend When a visitor chooses to send News, Articles, Reviews, etc, to a friend, the names and e-mail addresses are not logged. Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans will send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit our site. Woodworkweb.com - woodworking community - Free woodworking plans will never send another e-mail to the visitor or friend for any purpose.
Changes of our Policy If and when our policy statement changes, visitors with Memberships in our databases will be notified of the changes, and provided a link to this page to view the changes. If a visitor decides that our policy does not benefit them, they can use the opt-out option at anytime.
Prev
Next
000s2smodern
powered by social2s
Join Us On:
YouTube
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
Pinterest
Google+
Amazon  Store
Merchandise
About WoodWorkWeb
Contact UsAdvertise With UsAbout UsPrivacy StatementTerms of UseDisclaimer StatementAs an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchasesWoodworkweb is a participant in the GoAffPro Affiliate Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to the partner site
